<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent">

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/description_tv"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:padding="12dp"
        tools:text="It is a time of unrest in 1920s Europa. The ashes from the first great war still darken the snow. The capitalistic city-state known simply as The Factory, which fueled the war with heavily armored mechs, has closed its doors, drawing the attention of several nearby countries.&#10;&#10;Scythe is an engine-building game set in an alternate-history 1920s period. It is a time of farming and war, broken hearts and rusted gears, innovation and valor. In Scythe, each player represents a character from one of five factions of Eastern Europe who are attempting to earn their fortune and claim their faction's stake in the land around the mysterious Factory. Players conquer territory, enlist new recruits, reap resources, gain villagers, build structures, and activate monstrous mechs.&#10;&#10;Each player begins the game with different resources (power, coins, combat acumen, and popularity), a different starting location, and a hidden goal. Starting positions are specially calibrated to contribute to each factions uniqueness and the asymmetrical nature of the game (each faction always starts in the same place).&#10;&#10;Scythe gives players almost complete control over their fate. Other than each players individual hidden objective card, the only elements of luck or variability are encounter cards that players will draw as they interact with the citizens of newly explored lands. Each encounter card provides the player with several options, allowing them to mitigate the luck of the draw through their selection."
        android:textSize="18sp"
        android:textColor="@color/textColorPrimary"/>

</ScrollView>